import { Category } from 'src/app/interfaces/category.interface';

export default {
  name: 'Апрель',
  cards: [
    {
      "question": "exorbitant",
      "answer": "чрезмерный"
    },
    {
      "question": "former",
      "answer": "бывший"
    },
    {
      "question": "crows",
      "answer": "толпы"
    },
    {
      "question": "all over again",
      "answer": "опять с самого начала"
    },
    {
      "question": "get put off",
      "answer": "откладывать"
    },
    {
      "question": "substantially",
      "answer": "существенно"
    },
    {
      "question": "downsides",
      "answer": "недостатки"
    },
    {
      "question": "urgent",
      "answer": "срочный"
    },
    {
      "question": "to investigate",
      "answer": "исследовать"
    },
    {
      "question": "to exaggerate (экзаджерейт)",
      "answer": "преувеличивать"
    },
    {
      "question": "to appreciate",
      "answer": "ценить"
    },
    {
      "question": "merely",
      "answer": "просто"
    },
    {
      "question": "sufficient",
      "answer": "достаточно"
    },
    {
      "question": "conclusions",
      "answer": "заключения/выводы"
    },
    {
      "question": "to possess",
      "answer": "обладать"
    }
  ]
} as Category;
